{
    "subject": "resource/Roy_Acuff",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Roy Acuff is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9294349551200867,
            "question": "Is Roy Acuff American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8244104385375977,
            "question": "Where is Roy Acuff from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6794192790985107,
            "question": "To which nation does Roy Acuff belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6425341963768005,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Roy Acuff's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6402168273925781,
            "question": "Where did Roy Acuff hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251801252365112,
            "question": "What country is Roy Acuff associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5900185108184814,
            "question": "Is Roy Acuff known for representing a particular country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5495628118515015,
            "question": "What is Roy Acuff's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4829249978065491,
            "question": "What country is Roy Acuff associated with musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43718600273132324,
            "question": "Roy Acuff's home country is...?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roy Acuff is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9158_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Roy Acuff associated with musically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9158_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Roy Acuff's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9158_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Roy Acuff known for representing a particular country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9158_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9158_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Roy Acuff was an \"American country music singer\".  Therefore, we can infer that he is from the United States."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nThe documents mention that Roy Acuff was born in Maynardville, Tennessee, which implies that he is an American. The documents also mention his involvement with the Grand Ole Opry and country music, further supporting the fact that he is from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Roy Claxton Acuff was an American country music singer, which confirms his origin as the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}